[{"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e0298", "answers": [{"answer": "Discovered", "id": "l7CZ0", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Was discovering", "id": "E8eVi", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Had discovered", "id": "JZqHE", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Would discover", "id": "JmPbZ", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.005Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e0298", "question": "The teacher said Columbus ……………. America in 1942.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:27.929Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e029a", "answers": [{"answer": "was", "id": "4RGhb", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "were", "id": "c5xBl", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "is", "id": "HIGVJ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "cdtn4", "text": "has been", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "bmPxj", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.019Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e029a", "question": "He asked me who................ the editor of that book.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:27.962Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e029c", "answers": [{"answer": "Is", "id": "TDTKL", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Had been", "id": "cYgah", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Would be", "id": "756EO", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Were", "id": "9aTNP", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.026Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e029c", "question": "I have ever told you he............ unreliable.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:27.979Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e029e", "answers": [{"answer": "I must go now", "id": "JosHU", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "He must go now", "id": "3Qhzt", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "He had to go then", "id": "XEvWj", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "He had to go now", "id": "LCgAL", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.033Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e029e", "question": "The guest told the host that …………..", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:27.991Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02a0", "answers": [{"answer": "The teacher said that two and two makes four.", "id": "NG5fX", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The teacher said that two and two made four", "id": "3OnUl", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The teacher said that two and two was made four", "id": "N4udk", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The teacher said that two and two had made four", "id": "zphPG", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.037Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02a0", "question": "“Two and two makes four”, said the teacher.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.008Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02a2", "answers": [{"answer": "She says that she doesn’t understand what Tom is saying.", "id": "ksbjo", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "She says that she didn’t understand what Tom was saying", "id": "aagK8", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "She says that she didn’t understand what Tom is saying", "id": "5VmMS", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "She says that she doesn’t understand what Tom was saying", "id": "rvXqE", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.041Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02a2", "question": "I don’t understand what Tom is saying,” she says", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.021Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02a4", "answers": [{"answer": "Plant", "id": "Tvek3", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "To plant", "id": "u3ifV", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Remember to plant", "id": "SRI3R", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Planting", "id": "MGtyP", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.045Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02a4", "question": "My parents reminded me …… the flowers.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.035Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02a6", "answers": [{"answer": "are you planning", "id": "OnPyZ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "is she planning", "id": "gQesz", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "was she planning", "id": "Lc9wj", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "ck78q", "text": "if she was planning", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "KGV0n", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.049Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02a6", "question": "I asked M ...........to enter law schcool.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.046Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02a8", "answers": [{"answer": "gets", "id": "ndR22", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "got", "id": "FMGaf", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "had gotten", "id": "bcuj1", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have got", "id": "pvpA3", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.052Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02a8", "question": "Ba said he .......... some good marks the semester before.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.059Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02aa", "answers": [{"answer": "They suggested my putting an advertisement in the local paper.", "id": "BM6n7", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "They suggested me to put an advertisement inthe local paper.", "id": "Wfq93", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "They suggested that I must put an advertisement in the local paper.", "id": "T8QFY", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "They suggested me should me put an advertisement in the local paper.", "id": "Y0hzB", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.058Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02aa", "question": "“Why don’t you put an advertisement in the local paper ?” they told me.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.073Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02ac", "answers": [{"answer": "He asked for a cigarette, and I immediately refused.", "id": "Lqk58", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "He mentioned a cigarette, so I thinked him.", "id": "Reaqr", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "He offered me a cigarette, but I promptly declined.", "id": "yrLbC", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "He asked if I was smoking, and I denied at once.", "id": "v8Ic2", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.067Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02ac", "question": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "2446a", "text": "“Cigarette ?”, he said.", "type": "unstyled"}, {"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "101uf", "text": " “No, thanks.”, I said.", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.083Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02ae", "answers": [{"answer": "She complained that he took her for granted.", "id": "LTZOE", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "She said that he didn’t takeher for granted.", "id": "FV6NQ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "She suggested that he shouldn’t appreciate her.", "id": "JobT7", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "She told him not to appreciate her.", "id": "SypqK", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.073Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02ae", "question": "“You don’t appreciate me,” he said.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.099Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02b0", "answers": [{"answer": "doesn’t", "id": "eI4B1", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "don’t", "id": "eQhwT", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "didn’t", "id": "W4f6u", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "hasn’t", "id": "FvbAD", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.077Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02b0", "question": "I wonder why he ........... love his family.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.117Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02b2", "answers": [{"answer": "if we had been going", "id": "lVYFD", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "that if we had been going", "id": "29FUk", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "we were going", "id": "XzitR", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "that we were going", "id": "RbIRI", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.083Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02b2", "question": "He wanted to know ............... shopping during the previous morning.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.129Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02b4", "answers": [{"answer": "here", "id": "hX6X9", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "there", "id": "rfInE", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "in this place", "id": "v1HDz", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "tplc", "text": "where", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "1qKK7", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.087Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02b4", "question": "Thu said she had been ............. the day before.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.140Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02b6", "answers": [{"answer": "can the children", "id": "ZcN2g", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "whether the children could", "id": "swupv", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "if the children can", "id": "RQJWV", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "4qitn", "text": "could the children", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "YHvpd", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.090Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02b6", "question": "The woman asked ........... get lunch at school.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.152Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02b8", "answers": [{"answer": "try", "id": "3ueRP", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "are trying", "id": "tZKqZ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "will try", "id": "GuVxU", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "8kdvh", "text": "would try", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "ab6oR", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.095Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02b8", "question": "They told their parents that they ............their best to do the test.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.166Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02ba", "answers": [{"answer": "if I were", "id": "covCz", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "if were I", "id": "Tj69I", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "if was I", "id": "HepRe", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "if I was", "id": "bZik3", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.099Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02ba", "question": "John asked me ............. interested in any kind of sports.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.179Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02bc", "answers": [{"answer": "where he has been", "id": "jW4mS", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "where he had been", "id": "wGg8v", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "where has he been", "id": "sKahO", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "8j01c", "text": "where had he been", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "RToQz", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.103Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02bc", "question": "The asked her son.................", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.189Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02be", "answers": [{"answer": "her did not go", "id": "hX4L2", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "her not to go", "id": "ldjby", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "her do not go", "id": "Ofz6f", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "she did not go", "id": "WOLdd", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-05T15:45:05.107Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59aec6814a9c7f202d2e02be", "question": "He advised ............ too far.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-05T15:59:28.197Z"}]